[
  {
    "answerkey": 3,
    "option 3": "System Testing",
    "option 4": "Statement Coverage",
    "question": "Which of the following is a type of black-box testing?",
    "option 1": "Unit Testing",
    "option 2": "Integration Testing"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 2,
    "option 3": "Integration",
    "option 4": "Inspection",
    "question": "In software testing, which term refers to checking if the product meets customer needs?",
    "option 1": "Verification",
    "option 2": "Validation"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 4,
    "option 3": "Acceptance Testing",
    "option 4": "Debugging",
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a level of software testing?",
    "option 1": "Unit Testing",
    "option 2": "System Testing"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 1,
    "option 3": "Regression Testing",
    "option 4": "Performance Testing",
    "question": "Which type of testing is performed without executing the code?",
    "option 1": "Static Testing",
    "option 2": "Dynamic Testing"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 2,
    "option 3": "Unit Testing",
    "option 4": "Smoke Testing",
    "question": "Which of these is a non-functional testing type?",
    "option 1": "Regression Testing",
    "option 2": "Load Testing"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 3,
    "option 3": "Regression Testing",
    "option 4": "Alpha Testing",
    "question": "Which testing ensures that new code changes do not break existing functionality?",
    "option 1": "Sanity Testing",
    "option 2": "Unit Testing"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 3,
    "option 3": "Methodology",
    "option 4": "Method",
    "question": "Agile is a?",
    "option 1": "Test Stratrgy",
    "option 2": "Model"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 3,
    "option 3": "Test Implementation",
    "option 4": "Test completion activity",
    "question": "Which activity is not done by Test Manager?",
    "option 1": "Test Planning",
    "option 2": "Test Monitor and control"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 1,
    "option 3": "8",
    "option 4": "9",
    "question": "What is the count of STLC?",
    "option 1": "6",
    "option 2": "7"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 2,
    "option 3": "400",
    "option 4": "401",
    "question": "After an API request is sent, the server throws a error code saying internal server error in postman. Which is the posible HTTP request it sends? ",
    "option 1": "501",
    "option 2": "500"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 4,
    "option 3": "Load Testing",
    "option 4": "Penetration Testing",
    "question": "Brupsuit is used for?",
    "option 1": "API Testing",
    "option 2": "Manual Testing"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 3,
    "option 3": "Spike Test",
    "option 4": "Database Test",
    "question": "To find out the sudden increase of load in a sudden time, which test is done?",
    "option 1": "Load test",
    "option 2": "Stress Test"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 4,
    "option 3": "save()",
    "option 4": "flush()",
    "question": "What is the command for saving a JSON file?",
    "option 1": "read()",
    "option 2": "write()"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 1,
    "option 3": "Its a METHOD",
    "option 4": "Its a model",
    "question": "@Test annotation indicates?",
    "option 1": "Its a test ",
    "option 2": "Its a class"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 1,
    "option 3": "how well a system performs under its server",
    "option 4": "minimum and maximum boundary value ",
    "question": "What is capacity Testing?",
    "option 1": "ability to take load of number of users",
    "option 2": "capacity of a database to add new data"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 2,
    "option 3": "Capacity",
    "option 4": "Security",
    "question": "In which test, we keep user constant and time variable?",
    "option 1": "Stress",
    "option 2": "Load"
  }
]